("Uptown Girl" by Billy Joel)
♪ Uptown girl ♪
♪ She's been living in her uptown world ♪
♪ I bet she's never had a backstreet guy ♪
♪ I bet her momma never told her why ♪
♪ I'm gonna try for an uptown girl ♪
♪ She's been living in
her white-bred world ♪
♪ As long as anyone with hot blood can ♪
♪ And now she's looking
for a downtown man ♪
♪ That's what I am ♪
♪ And when she knows what ♪
♪ She wants from her time ♪
♪ And when she wakes up ♪
♪ And makes up her mind ♪
♪ She'll see I'm not so tough ♪
♪ Just because ♪
♪ I'm in love with an uptown girl ♪
♪ You know I've seen her
in her uptown world ♪
♪ She's getting tired
of her high-class toys ♪
♪ And all her presents
from her uptown boys ♪
♪ She's got a choice ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Uptown girl ♪
♪ You know I can't afford
to buy her pearls ♪
♪ But maybe someday
when my ship comes in ♪
♪ She'll understand what
kind of guy I've been ♪
♪ And then I'll win ♪
♪ And when she's walking ♪
♪ She's looking so fine ♪
♪ And when she's talking ♪
♪ She'll say that she's mine ♪
♪ She'll say I'm not so tough ♪
♪ Just because ♪
♪ I'm in love ♪
♪ With an uptown girl ♪
♪ She's been living in
her white-bred world ♪
♪ As long as anyone with hot blood can ♪
♪ And now she's looking
for a downtown man ♪
♪ That's what I am ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Uptown girl ♪
♪ She's my uptown girl ♪
♪ You know I'm in love ♪
♪ With an uptown girl ♪
♪ My uptown girl ♪
♪ You know I'm in love ♪
♪ With an uptown girl ♪
♪ My uptown girl ♪
♪ You know I'm in love ♪
♪ With an uptown girl ♪
♪ My uptown girl ♪
♪ You know I'm in love ♪
♪ With an uptown girl ♪